What do you want?
I just don't give a rat's ass.
(Howard:)Would that be a giant rat's ass?
(Sheldon:)For the record, giant rats are possible.
(Leonard:)Can we please talk
about something else?
(Leonard:)Maybe something vaguely related
to life as we know it on this planet?
Okay, how about this for a topic:
"Why is Leonard being a giant douche?"
(Howard:)Assuming giant douches are possible.
(Sheldon:)Of course they are.
Leonard's being one.
-Maybe he's having a spat with Penny.
-No. There was no spat.
(Howard:)-Oh, but something happened.
-I don't wanna talk about it.
(Sheldon:)But I sense you're going to and
I don't wanna hear about it. Excuse me.
(Howard:)What'd you do, Romeo?
Did you pour maple syrup
all over your body...
(Howard:)...and ask her if she was in the mood
for a short stack?
(Raj:)Think it would be funny
to put on her panties and jump around...
(Raj:)...but it wound up
just creeping her out?
(Leonard:)-What? No.
-Just asking, dude.